Guide to the Time Inc. Reference Files 1907-2015 (bulk 1933-2003) MS 3009-RG 3
New-York Historical Society
- Public Affairs: Contributions: Corporate (Offsite-box 561, Folder 11-12)
- Public Affairs: Time Edit: Time on Air (TV and Radio): 2010 (Offsite-box 561, Folder 13)
- Public Affairs: Time Edit: Time on Air (TV and Radio): 2011 (Offsite-box 561, Folder 14)
- Public Affairs: Time Edit: TIme on Air (TV and Radio): 2009 (Offsite-box 561, Folder 14-15)
- Public Affairs: Time Edit: Time on Air (TV and Radio): 2008 (Offsite-box 561, Folder 16-17)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: Exhibition Center: Misc.: 1961-1970 (Offsite-box 561, Folder 18-19)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc: Broadcast Publicity: 8/14/1989- (Offsite-box 561, Folder 20-21)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc: Time Incers On the Air: 5/5/1987-8/9/1989 (Offsite-box 561-562)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1992-2008 (Offsite-box 562, Folder 3)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: Corporate Communications: Article of the Week: 2009 (Offsite-box 562, Folder 4)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: Corporate Communications: Article of the Week: 2010 (Offsite-box 562, Folder 5)
- Public Affairs: Corporate Communications: Article of the Week: 2011 [empty] (Offsite-box 562, Folder 6)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: Corporate Communications: Four Questions: 2009 (Offsite-box 562, Folder 7)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: Corporate Communications: Four Questions: 2010 (Offsite-box 562, Folder 8)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: Corporate Communications: Four Questions: 2011 [empty] (Offsite-box 562, Folder 9)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: Corporate Communications: Time Inc. University: 2009 (Offsite-box 562, Folder 10)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: Corporate Communications: Time Inc. University: 2010 [empty] (Offsite-box 562, Folder 11)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: Corporate Communications: Time Inc. University: 2011 [empty] (Offsite-box 562, Folder 12)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: Corporate Cultural Affairs (Offsite-box 562, Folder 13-14)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: Exhibition Center Attendance (Offsite-box 562, Folder 15-16)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: Exhibition Center: Misc.: 1960 and Previous (Offsite-box 562, Folder 17)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: Exhibitions: Michaelangelo (Offsite-box 562, Folder 18)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: The Search for Alexander: Financial Agreements/Legal Agreements (Offsite-box 562)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: The Search for Alexander: Financial Agreements/Legal Agreements [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R6)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: Misc.: From Time to Time (Offsite-box 562, Folder 20)
- Public Affairs: Time: Newstours: 1963-1999 (Offsite-box 562, Folder 21)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: The Search for Alexander: Publicity (Offsite-box 562, Folder 22)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: The Search for Alexander: Misc.: Exhibition (Offsite-box 562, Folder 23)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: Exhibitions: Misc. (Offsite-box 562, Folder 23)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: Misc. (Offsite-box 562, Folder 24)
- Public Affairs: HRL-Judged Competitions (Offsite-box 562, Folder 25)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: General Electric Panel Presentation: Public Understanding and Defense: 1960 (Offsite-box 562, Folder 26)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc and Time Warner: Time to Read: 1985- (Offsite-box 562, Folder 27)
- Public Affairs: Time Warner Inc: 1992-2008 (Offsite-box 562, Folder 28)
- Publishers Information Bureau (Offsite-box 562, Folder 31)
- Publications (Offsite-box 562, Folder 29)
- Publishers' Committee: Meetings: 1947 (Offsite-box 562, Folder 30)
- Publishers Information Bureau (Offsite-box 562, Folder 31)
- Quality Magazine (Offsite-box 563, Folder 1)
- Quotes: Time Inc.: Editors and Executives [empty] (Offsite-box 563, Folder 2)
- Quotes: Time Inc.: H.R. Luce (Offsite-box 563, Folder 3)
- Real Estate: Misc. (Offsite-box 563, Folder 4)
- Real Simple: Index: 2000-2003 (Offsite-box 563, Folder 5)
- Real Simple: Misc. (Offsite-box 563, Folder 6)
- Records (Offsite-box 563, Folder 7)
- Reminiscences (Offsite-box 563, Folder 8)
- Selling Areas: Marketing, Inc. (Offsite-box 563, Folder 9)
- Southern Accents [empty] (Offsite-box 563, Folder 10)
- Southern Living [empty] (Offsite-box 563, Folder 11)
- Southern Progress Corporation (Offsite-box 563, Folder 12)
- Speeches: Index: by Celia Sugarman (Offsite-box 563, Folder 13)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising: Misc. (Offsite-box 563, Folder 14)
- Sports Illustrated: Advertising: Rate Cards (Offsite-box 563, Folder 15)
- Sports Illustrated: Circulation (Offsite-box 563, Folder 16)
- Sports Illustrated: Edit: Regional Edit Inserts: 1971 (Offsite-box 563, Folder 17)
- Sports Illustrated: Edit: Regional Edit Inserts: 1972 (Offsite-box 563, Folder 18)
- Sports Illustrated: Edit: Regional Edit Inserts: 1975 (Offsite-box 563, Folder 19)
- Sports Illustrated: Edit: Regional Edit Inserts: 1973 (Offsite-box 563, Folder 20)
- Sports Illustrated: Edit: Regional Edit Inserts: 1974 (Offsite-box 563, Folder 21)
- Sports Illustrated: Edit: Misc. (Offsite-box 563, Folder 22)
- Sports Illustrated: History (Offsite-box 563, Folder 23-24)
- Sports Illustrated: History: Original employee list: 1954 (Offsite-box 563, Folder 25)
- Sports Illustrated: Index: 1954 (Offsite-box 677, Folder 1)
- Sports Illustrated: Index: 1955 (Offsite-box 677, Folder 2)
- Sports Illustrated: Index: 1956 (Offsite-box 677, Folder 3)
  One folder, marked "Empty".
- Sports Illustrated: Index: 1957 (Offsite-box 677, Folder 4)
- Sports Illustrated: Index: 1958 (Offsite-box 677, Folder 5)
- Sports Illustrated: Index: 1959 (Offsite-box 677, Folder 6)
- Sports Illustrated: Index: 1960 (Offsite-box 677, Folder 7)
- Sports Illustrated: Index: 1961 (Offsite-box 677, Folder 7)
- Sports Illustrated: Index: 1962 (Offsite-box 677, Folder 9)
- Sports Illustrated: Index: 1963 (Offsite-box 677, Folder 10)
- Sports Illustrated: Index: 1964 (Offsite-box 677, Folder 11)
- Sports Illustrated: Index: 1965 (Offsite-box 677, Folder 12)
- Sports Illustrated: Index: 1966 (Offsite-box 677, Folder 13)
- Sports Illustrated: Index: 1967 (Offsite-box 677, Folder 14)
- Sports Illustrated: Index: 1968 (Offsite-box 677, Folder 15)
- Sports Illustrated: Index: 1969 (Offsite-box 677, Folder 16)
- Sports Illustrated: Index: 1970 (Offsite-box 677, Folder 17)
- Sports Illustrated: Index: 1971 (Offsite-box 677, Folder 18)
- Sports Illustrated: Index: 1972 (Offsite-box 677, Folder 18)
- Sports Illustrated: Swimsuit Issue (Offsite-box 563, Folder 26)
- Sports Illustrated: Covers: Misc. (Offsite-box 563, Folder 27)
- Sports Illustrated: Prospectus Copies (Offsite-box 564, Folder 1)
- Sports Illustrated: Year in Sports, The: Special Issue: Annual (Offsite-box 564, Folder 2)
- Sports Illustrated: Index (Offsite-box 564, Folder 3-4)
- Sports Illustrated: for Women: Misc.: March 2000-Dec. 2002 (Offsite-box 564, Folder 5)
- Sports Illustrated: on Campus: 2003 (Offsite-box 564, Folder 6)
- Sports Illustrated: For Kids: Covers: Misc. (Offsite-box 564, Folder 7)
- Sports Illustrated: For Kids: Misc. (Offsite-box 564, Folder 8)
- Suede (Offsite-box 564, Folder 9)
- Sunset Publishing Corporation: Misc. (Offsite-box 564, Folder 10)
- Sunset Press (Offsite-box 564, Folder 11)
- Synapse Group Inc. (Offsite-box 564, Folder 12)
- Teen People: Misc. (Offsite-box 564, Folder 13)
- Teen People: Book Club (Offsite-box 564, Folder 14)
- Teletext (Offsite-box 564, Folder 15)
- Temple-Eastex: Eastex- A Chronicle, 1936-1957 by Charles Stillman (Offsite-box 564, Folder 16)
- Temple-Eastex: Misc. (Offsite-box 564, Folder 17-19)
- This Old House: Misc.: 1994- (Offsite-box 564, Folder 20)
- Time: Advertising: Rate Cards: 1970-1979 (Offsite-box 564, Folder 21-22)
- Time: Advertising: Rate Cards: 1990-1999 (Offsite-box 564, Folder 23)
- Time: Advertising: Rate Cards: 2000-2004 (Offsite-box 565, Folder 1)
- Time: Advertising: Rate Cards: 1980-1989 (Offsite-box 565, Folder 2-3)
- Time Customer Service, Inc. (Offsite-box 565, Folder 4)
- Time Customer Service, Inc.: Keylines Newsletter: 11/87 (Issue 1)-9/90 (Vol. 4, No. 8) (Offsite-box 565, Folder 5)
- Time Digital: Misc. (Offsite-box 565, Folder 6)
- Time Distrubution Service (Offsite-box 565, Folder 7)
- Time Distribution Services (TDS): Newsletter: Checkout (Offsite-box 565, Folder 8)
- Time-Hachette (Offsite-box 565, Folder 9)
- Time Inc.: Audiotapes (Offsite-box 565, Folder 11)
- Time Inc.: Executive's papers: Collections outside Time (Offsite-box 565, Folder 12)
- Time Inc.: Custom Publishing: 1999- (Offsite-box 565, Folder 13)
- Time Inc.: Multimedia/News Media: Misc. (Offsite-box 565, Folder 14)
- Time Inc.: Misc.: 1993- (Offsite-box 565, Folder 15)
- Time Inc.: History (Offsite-box 565, Folder 16)
- Time Inc.: Quarterly Reports: 1970-1987 (Offsite-box 565, Folder 17-18)
- Time Inc.: Restructurings: Misc. announcement, memos, and clips: 1960- (Offsite-box 565, Folder 19)
- Time Inc. Ventures (Offsite-box 565, Folder 20)
- Time-Life Alumni Society (Offsite-box 565, Folder 21)
- Time-Life Alumni Society: Luncheon Speakers (Offsite-box 565, Folder 22)
- Time-Life Alumni Society: Speeches (Offsite-box 565, Folder 23)
- Time-Life Books, Inc.: Incorporation (Offsite-box 565)
- Time-Life Books, Inc.: Incorporation [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R6)
- Time-Life Books Division: Historical Material (Offsite-box 565, Folder 25)
- Time-Life Books: Historical Overview: from JD McSweeney Files (Offsite-box 565, Folder 26)
- Time-Life Books: Oral history of Life World Library (Offsite-box 565, Folder 27)
  Scope and Contents
  In 1970, Time-Life Books founding editor Norman Ross conducted interviews with Time-Life Books art director Edward Hamilton and Life World Library editor Oliver Allen about the creation of Life World Library, the first series published by Time-Life Books. Box 565 includes summaries of the discussion. These tapes were initially deposited with the Yale University archives, but transferred to Time Inc. in 1980.
- Time-Life Books: Oral history of Life World Library: Audiotape Reels [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box 3452)
  Includes audiovisual material:
  6 audiotape reels: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. for Oliver E. Allen
  6 audiotape reels: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. for Edward A. Hamilton
- Time-Life Books: Lists (Offsite-box 566-567)
- Time-Life Books: Nicholas on Alexandria (N.O.A.) (Offsite-box 566, Folder 4)
- Time-Life Films: Catalogues (Offsite-box 566, Folder 5-6)
- Time-Life Films: Films Titles Lists (Offsite-box 566, Folder 7)
- Time-Life Books: Personnel: Alexandria Staff: October 1997 (Offsite-box 566, Folder 8)
- Time-Life Books: Publicity Releases (Offsite-box 566, Folder 9)
- Time-Life Books: Misc. (Offsite-box 566, Folder 10-12)
- Time-Life Broadcast: News Releases (Offsite-box 566, Folder 13)
- Time-Life Broadcast: Misc. (Offsite-box 566, Folder 14)
- Time-Life Films: Misc. (Offsite-box 566, Folder 15)
- Time-Life News Service: Correspondents Lists: 1949 and Before (Offsite-box 566, Folder 16)
- Time-Life News Service: Correspondents Insignia: World War II (Offsite-box 567, Folder 1)
- Time-Life News Service: Foreign (Offsite-box 567, Folder 2)
- Time-Life News Service: Correspondents Lists: 1950-1959 (Offsite-box 567, Folder 5)
- Time-Life News Service: Correspondents Lists: 1960-1969 (Offsite-box 567, Folder 6-7)
- Time-Life News Service: Correspondents Lists: 1970-1979 (Offsite-box 567, Folder 3-4)
- Time-Life News Service: Correspondents Lists: 1980-1989 (Offsite-box 567, Folder 8)
- Time-Life News Service: Domestic (Including Canada) (Offsite-box 567, Folder 9)
- Time-Life News Service: Misc. (Offsite-box 567, Folder 10-11)
  A/V: CD-R labeled "TIme-Life News Service Reunion- 2011. Photographs of Alumni, donated by John Stacks".
- Time-Life Television (Offsite-box 567, Folder 12)
- Time-Life Video (Offsite-box 567, Folder 13)
- Time Bureau Chiefs' Report: Supplement: Circulation Promotion (Offsite-box 567, Folder 16)
- Time: Circulation: Mailings: Returns Reports (Offsite-box 567, Folder 17)
- Time: Circulation: A.B.C. Statements: 1981- (Offsite-box 567, Folder 18-19)
- Time: Circulation: A.B.C. Statements: 1924-1980 (Offsite-box 568, Folder 1)
- Time: Circulation: Misc. (Offsite-box 568, Folder 3-4)
- Time: Copyrights (Offsite-box 568, Folder 5)
- Time: Covers: Brochures and Printed Pieces (Offsite-box 568, Folder 6)
- Time: Covers: Artists (Offsite-box 568, Folder 7)
- Time: Covers: Lists by Category (Offsite-box 568, Folder 8)
- Time: Covers: Collectors (Offsite-box 568, Folder 9)
- Time: Covers: Corporate Subjects (Time Inc., TW, AOLTW) (Offsite-box 568, Folder 10)
- Time: Covers: Exhibitions: Misc. (Offsite-box 568, Folder 11)
- Time: Covers: Lists: Alphabetical: 1923-1963 (Offsite-box 568, Folder 12-13)
- Time: Covers: Lists by Artist (Offsite-box 568, Folder 14)
- Time: Covers: Lists: Chronological (Offsite-box 568, Folder 15-16)
- Time: Lists: Domestic and International Cover Comparisons (Offsite-box 568, Folder 17)
- Time: Man of the Year National Portrait Gallery Booklet (Offsite-box 568, Folder 18)
- Time: Covers: Man of the Year (Offsite-box 568, Folder 19-20)
- Time: Covers: Misc: 1938-1989 (Offsite-box 569, Folder 1)
- Time: Covers: Misc.: 1990- (Offsite-box 569, Folder 2)
- Time: Covers: Movies and Television (Offsite-box 569, Folder 3)
- Time: Covers: Specific Subjects (Offsite-box 569, Folder 4)
- Time-Life Video: Catalogues (Offsite-box 569, Folder 5-8)
- Time: Advertising: Misc. (Offsite-box 569, Folder 9)
- Time: Advertising: Rate Cards: 1924-1929 (Offsite-box 569, Folder 10)
- Time: Advertising: Rate Cards: 1930-1939 (Offsite-box 569, Folder 11)
- Time: Advertising: Rate Cards: 1940-1949 (Offsite-box 569, Folder 12)
- Time: Advertising: Rate Cards: 1960-1969 (Offsite-box 569, Folder 14)
- Time: Covers: Never Ran (Offsite-box 569, Folder 15)
- Time: Current Affairs Test (Offsite-box 569, Folder 16)
- Time: Edit: Book Reviews (Offsite-box 569, Folder 17)
- Time: Edit: Errors Reports: May 2002 (Offsite-box 569, Folder 18)
- Time: Edit: Departments (Chronology of) (Offsite-box 569, Folder 20)
- Time: Edit: Graphics (Offsite-box 569, Folder 21)
- Time: Edit: Graphics redesign 1992 (Offsite-box 569, Folder 22)
- Time: Edit: Ideology Report: 1935-1945 (Offsite-box 569, Folder 23)
- Time: Edit: Large Print Edition (Offsite-box 569, Folder 24)
- Time: Edit: Misc.: Ends 1989 (Offsite-box 570, Folder 1)
- Time: Edit: Operating Expenses (Offsite-box 570, Folder 5)
- Time: Edit: Man of the Year (Offsite-box 570, Folder 6-7)
- Time: Edit: Mastheads (Offsite-box 570, Folder 8)
- Time: Edit: Person of the Century: 1999 (Offsite-box 570, Folder 9-10)
- Time: Edit: Person of the Year (Offsite-box 570, Folder 11)
- Time: Edit: Man of the Year: Loan of MOY Reagan Portrait to the National Portrait Gallery (Offsite-box 570)
- Time: Edit: Man of the Year: Loan of MOY Reagan Portrait to the National Portrait Gallery [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R6)
- Time: Edit: Personnel Lists (Offsite-box 570, Folder 13)
- Time: Edit: Research (Offsite-box 570, Folder 14-15)
- Time: Edit: Series (Offsite-box 570, Folder 16)
- Time: Edit: Sport (Offsite-box 570, Folder 17)
- Time: Edit: Style: Book (Offsite-box 570, Folder 18)
- Time: Edit: Style: Misc. (Offsite-box 559, 570)
- Time: Edit: Time Pieces (Offsite-box 559, Folder 2)
- Time4Media: Misc. (Offsite-box 559, Folder 3)
- Time: Histories: 1957 and Before (Offsite-box 559, Folder 4-6)
- Time: Histories: 1958 and Later (Offsite-box 559, Folder 7-8)
- Time: History: Research (Offsite-box 559, Folder 9)
- Time: Index: 1939 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 10)
- Time: Index: 1940 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 11)
- Time: Index: 1941 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 12)
- Time: Index: 1942 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 13)
- Time: Index: 1943 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 14)
- Time: Index: 1944 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 15)
- Time: Index: 1945 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 16)
- Time: Index: 1946 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 17)
- Time: Index: 1947 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 18)
- Time: Index: 1948 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 19)
- Time: Index: 1949 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 20)
- Time: Index: 1950 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 21)
- Time: Index: 1951 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 22)
- Time: Index: 1952 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 23)
- Time: Index: 1953 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 24)
- Time: Index: 1954 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 25)
- Time: Index: 1955 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 26)
- Time: Index: 1956 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 27)
- Time: Index: 1957 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 28)
- Time: Index: 1958 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 29)
- Time: Index: 1959 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 30)
- Time: Index: 1960 (Offsite-box 559, Folder 31)
- Time: Index: 1961 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 1)
- Time: Index: 1962 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 2)
- Time: Index: 1963 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 3)
- Time: Index: 1964 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 4)
- Time: Index: 1965 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 5)
- Time: Index: 1966 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 6)
- Time: Index: 1967 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 7)
- Time: Index: 1968 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 8)
- Time: Index: 1969 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 9)
- Time: Index: 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 10)
- Time: Index: 1973 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 11)
- Time: Index: 1974 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 12)
- Time: Index: 1975 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 13)
- Time: Index: 1976 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 14)
- Time: Index: 1977 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 15)
- Time: Letters Department (Offsite-box 571, Folder 16)
- Time: Letters Department: Instruction Manual: 1962 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 17)
- Time: Letters Department: Manuals (Offsite-box 571, Folder 18-19)
- Time: Letters Reports: 2000-2001 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 20)
- Time: Letters Reports: 2002 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 21)
- Time: Letters Reports: 2003 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 22)
- Time: Letters Reports: 2004 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 23)
- Time: Letters Reports: 2005 (Offsite-box 571, Folder 24)
- Time: Letters Reports: 2006- (Offsite-box 571, Folder 25)
- Time: Marked Copy Lists: 1999-2002 (Offsite-box 571-572)
- Time: Marked Copy Lists 2003 (Offsite-box 572, Folder 2-3)
- Time: Marked Copy List 2004 (Offsite-box 572, Folder 4)
- Time: Misc. (Offsite-box 572, Folder 5)
- Time: Pony Editions (Offsite-box 572, Folder 6)
- Time: Production (Offsite-box 572, Folder 7)
- Time: Production: Bert Chapman Scrapbook (Offsite-box 572, Folder 8)
- Time: Prospectus Copies (Offsite-box 572, Folder 9)
- Time: Publishing (Offsite-box 572, Folder 10)
- Time: Statistical History (Offsite-box 572, Folder 11)
- Time: Story Behind the Story: 1964 and 1965 (Offsite-box 572, Folder 12-13)
- Time: Style and Design (Offsite-box 572, Folder 14)
- Time Canada: A.B.C. Reports (Offsite-box 572, Folder 15)
- Time Canada: Advertising Rate Cards: 1940-1949 (Offsite-box 572, Folder 16)
- Time Canada: Advertising Rate Cards: 1950-1959 (Offsite-box 572, Folder 17)
- Time Canada: Advertising Rate Cards: 1960-1969 (Offsite-box 572, Folder 18)
- Time Canada: Advertising Rate Cards: 1970-1979 (Offsite-box 572, Folder 19)
- Time Canada: Advertising Rate Cards: 1980-1999 (Offsite-box 573, Folder 1)
- Time Canada: Misc. (Offsite-box 573, Folder 2)
- Time International: A.B.C. Reports: Latin America: 1941-1972 (Offsite-box 573, Folder 3)
- Time International: A.B.C. Statements: Asia (Offsite-box 573, Folder 4)
- Time International: A.B.C. Statements: Atlantic (Offsite-box 573, Folder 5)
- Time International: A.B.C. Statements: Worldwide (Offsite-box 573, Folder 7)
- Time International: Advertising Rate Cards: Asia and South Pacific: 1946-1959 (Offsite-box 573, Folder 6)
- Time International: Advertising Rate Cards: Asia and South Pacific: 1960-1969 (Offsite-box 573, Folder 9)
- Time International: Advertising Rate Cards: Asia and South Pacific: 1970-1979 (Offsite-box 573, Folder 10)
- Time International: Advertising Rate Cards: Asia and South Pacific: 1980-1989 (Offsite-box 573, Folder 11)
- Time International: Advertising Rate Cards: Asia and South Pacific: 1990-1999 (Offsite-box 573, Folder 12)
- Time International: Advertising Rate Cards: Atlantic and Worldwide: 1943-1949 (Offsite-box 573, Folder 13)
- Time International: Advertising Rate Cards: Atlantic and Worldwide: 1950-1959 (Offsite-box 573, Folder 14)
- Time International: Advertising Rate Cards: Atlantic and Worldwide: 1961-1969 (Offsite-box 573, Folder 15-16)
- Time International: Advertising Rate Cards: 1970-1979 (Offsite-box 573, Folder 17)
- Time International: Advertising Rate Cards: Atlantic and Worldwide: 1980-1989 (Offsite-box 573, Folder 18-19)
- Time International: Advertising Rate Cards: Atlantic and Worldwide: 1990-1999 (Offsite-box 573, Folder 20)
- Time International: Advertising Rate Cards: Atlantic and Worldwide: 2000-2006 (Offsite-box 573, Folder 21)
- Time International: Advertising Rate Cards: Latin America: 1941-1972 (Offsite-box 574, Folder 1)
- Time International: Advertising Rates: Green Book: 1972 (Offsite-box 574, Folder 2)
- Time International: Advertising Rates: Green Book: 1973 (Offsite-box 574, Folder 3)
- Time International: Advertising Rates: Green Book: 1974 (Offsite-box 574, Folder 4)
- Time International: Advertising Rates: Misc. (Offsite-box 574, Folder 5-6)
- Time International: Pony Edition (Wartime): Covers: 1943 (Offsite-box 574, Folder 7)
- Time International: Edit Summaries (Offsite-box 574, Folder 8)
- Time International: Overseas and Pony Editions (Offsite-box 574, Folder 9)
- Time International: Misc.: 1959 and Before (Offsite-box 574, Folder 10)
- Time International: Misc.: 1961 and Later (Offsite-box 574, Folder 12-13)
- Time for Kids: Misc. (Offsite-box 574, Folder 14)
- Time Learning Ventures (Offsite-box 574, Folder 15)
- Time dot Com (Offsite-box 574, Folder 16)
- Time Inc.: History: Trivia (Offsite-box 574, Folder 17)
- Time Publishing Ventures: 1986-1991 (Offsite-box 574, Folder 18)
- Time Publishing Ventures: 1997 (Offsite-box 574, Folder 19)
- Time: Staff Contributors List (Offsite-box 574-575)
- Time: Staff Contributors List: 2008 (Offsite-box 575, Folder 2)
- Time: Staff Contributors List: 2009 (Offsite-box 575, Folder 3)
- Time: Staff Contributors List: 2010 (Offsite-box 575, Folder 4)
- Time: Staff Contributors List: 2011 (Offsite-box 575, Folder 5-6)
- Time: Staff Contributors List: 2012 (Offsite-box 575, Folder 7-8)
- Time: Staff Contributors List: 2013 (Offsite-box 575, Folder 9)
- Time: Telephone Marketing Inc. (Offsite-box 575, Folder 10)
- TWX: Internal Time Warner employee newsletter: 1998-2000 (Offsite-box 575, Folder 11-12)
- Time Warner Cable Group: Full Service Network (Offsite-box 575, Folder 13)
- Time Warner Cable Group: New York 1 News Channel (Offsite-box 575, Folder 14)
- Time Warner Cable Group: Quantum Service (Offsite-box 575, Folder 15)
- Time Warner Cable Group: Misc. (Offsite-box 575, Folder 16-17)
- Time Warner Cable Group: Misc. (Offsite-box 2220, Folder 3)
- Time Warner Digital Media: Misc. (Offsite-box 575, Folder 18)
- Time Warner Enterprises: (Offsite-box 575, Folder 19)
- Time Warner Enterprises: Court TV (Offsite-box 575, Folder 20)
- Time Warner Entertainment: Misc. (Offsite-box 575, Folder 21)
- Time Warner Entertainment: Toshiba, C. Itoh: Partnership announcement press clips: 1991 (Offsite-box 575, Folder 22)
- Time Warner Inc.: Annual Meetings: 1992- (Offsite-box 576, Folder 1)
- Time Warner Inc.: Calendars: 1995 (Offsite-box 576, Folder 2-4)
- Time Warner Inc.: Companies and Subsidaries: A-C (Offsite-box 576, Folder 5)
- Time Warner Inc.: Companies and Subsidaries: D-International (Offsite-box 576, Folder 6)
- Time Warner Inc.: Companies and Subsidaries: J-Museum Collections, Inc (Offsite-box 576, Folder 7)
- Time Warner Inc.: Companies and Subsidaries: N-S (Offsite-box 576, Folder 8)
- Time Warner Inc.: Companies and Subsidaries: T-Time-Life (Offsite-box 576, Folder 9)
- Time Warner Inc.: Companies and Subsidaries: U-Z (Offsite-box 576, Folder 10)
- Time Warner Inc: History (Offsite-box 576, Folder 11)
- Time Warner Inc.: Quarterly Reports (Offsite-box 576, Folder 12)
- Time Warner Inc.: Subsidaries List: 1981-1987 (Offsite-box 576, Folder 15-16)